[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 32]
Tree Fairy.
You always thought
that he and I were really in love.
But what about now?
Is this the ending of
true love?
What is the difference
between his actions and those of the animals?
Is it really because immortals are different from demons?
It turned out
those what the Masters said
were correct.
I knew
that you simply looked down on demons
in your heart.
I'm a demon, so what?
In the Three Realms,
except your brother and God of the Sun,
everyone surrenders to me.
Those so called Masters...
Saying that immortals are different from demons...
When I attack Immortal Palace
and they all kneel in front of me,
you will know
that
I'm much more honorable than they are.
Demon King.
Whether you pretended to be a lake demon to deceive me,
or conquered the Three Realms to prove yourself,
you were wrong.
People like you
don't know the difference between honorable and humble.
Let me tell you,
those who care about the common people are honorable,
and those who kill innocent people are humble.
I, Ze Shui,
am ashamed to have married such a despicable person as you.
Say it again!
All right!
I am ashamed
to have married such a despicable person as you.
May you
never see me again
forever.
Ze Shui!
How dare you treat me like this?
How could you do this to me?
Do you know
that I pretended to be a lake demon to deceive you,
and conquered the Three Realms to prove myself
just to prove that you did not marry the wrong person?
Even if I am a demon,
I am still your husband,
and the best!
Supreme Gods
and Immortals
are no match for me.
None of them deserve to compare with me!
So
Immortal Ze Shui
committed suicide afterwards?
Yes.
At that time,
two Supreme Gods were in retreat.
God of the Moonlight sensed her danger
and immediately went over.
But...
he was still late.
Therefore, the curse he set was extremely powerful.
The people of Aquatic Demons have tried their best,
but they couldn't break it.
But none of this has anything to do with you.
The reason I am telling you this today
is to let you know
that demons are evil.
I know
that Fu has helped you in the human world,
but as the general of the Demons,
he is cruel by nature.
Luo Ning,
I know you want to repay him,
and it's rare that he's willing to listen to you.
If one day
he ever wants to do bad things again,
you have to persuade him.
For Fu,
you are the only one who can lead him to kindness.
Master,
don't you have ten thousand years of immortal power?
Can't you
make this pill
smaller?
It's not my fault.
There is one ingredient missing in it.
The Star Stone sent by He Na
was very difficult to melt.
It's not easy that I can make this pill.
He Na is such a nice guy.
Star Stones are so rare,
but he sent it generously.
Yes.
We'd better repay him as soon as possible.
He didn't ask you to repay him.
You're right.
He Na
is really nice.
He's just troublesome occasionally.
If he didn't give you the Six-star Brilliant Array,
you wouldn't need Master to help you replenish your body.
Wait, what are you doing here?
I can't let Immortal know.
He would
have killed me
if he knew
I delivered medicine to He Na.
He Na lost a hand because of me,
and suffered such a serious injury.
I feel very guilty about it.
You want to hide it from Immortal Luo Ge,
and you're acting like a thief.
Which thief are you talking about?
No, no, no.
What?  Don't listen to his...
Nonsense.
I... Why... why are you here?
Shouldn't... shouldn't you be
recuperating at Palace Chongyang?
Why are you here?
But why do I feel
that you are just acting like a thief?
Am I?
What's in the box?
Show me.
I thought a thief had come to Xiyin Mountain.
It turned out that the thief was not from outside,
but someone we know.
What... what are you talking about?
These are all my own stuff.
Can't I give... give them away?
I...
I... I'm just an errand runner.
I'm just a looker-on.
She is the mastermind.
You...
Since you are willing to do it,
help me get this to him.
This is the spirit vein of Water Dragon.
Although it's not as good as He Na's Demon King spirit vein,
it's close enough.
It's good for his hand.
It turns out that you have noticed it.
Have you been looking for it for a long time?
He Na is also my friend.
It turns out
that you are also a person who cares about friends.
I can't let you always pay people back
because you feel sorry for them, right?
Mr. Tai,
how long has it been since Luo Ning left?
I don't think it's been long.
I made an agreement with her
that no matter what happened to her after she went back,
she would come back to see me.
I think
she must have forgotten me this time.
Next time she comes back,
I will definitely trap her
so that she can never leave me.
General Fu,
you are just saying things in anger.
It's useless to say so.
If Fairy Luo Ning is really angry about your words,
you definitely have to
apologize to her.
Shut up!
General Fu.
It seems that someone from Immortal Palace has come.
Luo Ning!
This is the spirit vein of Water Dragon that Immortal specially found for you.
Please convey my gratitude to Immortal for me.
Liu Shao is very careful.
The medicinal herbs and supplements she sent
are very suitable for me.
It turned out that these were sent by Liu Shao.
Brother.
Can you stop treating that girl as a treasure?
She doesn't even care about you.
Look.
She can make you so happy
by just sending these crap.
Fu.
What are you talking about?
These are collected by Liu Shao
from Immortal Palace and the mortal world.
She put a lot of effort into it.
How could you say that?
Are you unhappy
that you failed to kill them?
What are you talking about, you old demon?
I didn't say it.
It was… Master Shang.
What did he say?
He said
that Moon Poison came from Xie Lingqi
and later used by Bai Feng.
The only one who could instruct them at the same time
and had the motive to be enemies
with Luo Ge and Liu Shao was Fu.
What you are saying now
is just baseless
speculation.
This is not my speculation.
Anyway,
Master Shang
wouldn't think so for no reason.
They must have heard something.
That's the truth.
By the way,
Master Shang also said
that you may not be innocent as well,
because you were not afraid of Moon Poison.
Maybe
you were doing this to get close to Liu Shao
and had other plans.
It's fine if you just slander me,
don't slander my brother!
Fu.
Let him go!
Even if the immortal world and the demon world are at war,
killing the envoy is forbidden.
I just ran errands to deliver the medicine
and almost got killed.
Fu!
How dare you pinch my neck?
I'm going to learn that
and strangle him too!
Bai Feng?
Fu is completely different
from his brother.
How could they two be brothers?
I'll tell Liu Shao
and let her be careful of Fu.
Master.
Fairy Luo Ning.
I just
heard you mention Fu.
What happened to him?
I almost forgot.
Did you know Fu very well
when you were in mortal world?
Yes.
Listen to me.
You should stay away from him.
What's going on?
Did he do something
against Immortal Palace?
Guess who I saw at the Moon Washing Pond
when I returned from the demon world?
Who?
Brother.
You don't really believe
that grass demon's nonsense, do you?
I probably know more
than Wan Sui.
Xie Lingqi
just handed Moon Poison
to the person under Four Seasons Monument.
I'd like to know
when you got in touch
with
that person.
So what?
As long as he could help my people,
I could cooperate with him and use him.
I don't care who he is.
What about Bai Feng and Xie Lingqi?
They have nothing to do with me.
Stop lying!
We may not be able to find Bai Feng yet,
but Xie Lingqi has already repented.
Do you want me to take you to confront him?
Xie Lingqi...
I did take advantage of him for a while.
But he humiliated you before,
so what's wrong with me using him
to teach Immortal Palace a lesson?
You used Xie Lingqi
to assassinate Liu Shao and Zhuo Qiuxian.
I tried my best to save you,
and promised them that I would discipline you strictly.
Now,
you did this again.
How do you want me to explain to Immortal Palace and Luo Ge?
Brother.
You are a demon.
It is enough for you, Demon King,
to maintain the peace of the demon world.
You don't need to explain anything to anyone.
If the Three Realms are in chaos,
our demon world will also be affected.
Guards!
-Yes. -Yes.
Fu was impulsive and reckless,
and has violated orders.
Whip him harshly
as a warning to others.
Luo Ning.
My brother punished me again today.
Among the Three Realms,
only you are close to me.
But you cruelly left me for so long.
Fu,
what are you plotting with Bai Feng again?
If I'm the only one who can lead you to kindness,
I can't let you go on making mistakes.
Fu,
I'll find out
who you really are
with my own eyes.
Luo Ge.
Guess what I have prepared for you.
I can't wait.
Luo Ge, don't bother.
You can only walk on the path
that I have drawn for you.
Immortal Luo Ge isn't that powerful either.
No.
I can't let it be messed up like this.
I must find it as soon as possible.
Master has only left for a few hours.
What brings you here again?
I want to figure something out,
so I need to be invisible.
Among Demon Palace,
your water energy
is the best at covering up the aura.
Along
with the invisible perfume I made,
I should be able to become invisible.
Are you trying to investigate Fu?
He didn't flirt with other girls.
Would you lend it to me or not?
Of course.
General Fu,
by the time you see your brother,
Bai Feng has already arrived.
Bai Feng?
Has anyone noticed?
There is a boundary around,
no one will see her.
Okay.
Fu.
I didn't ask you to come.
Why are you here?
Don't worry.
I've set up a boundary here.
The one from Immortal Palace asked me to find you,
saying that with your help,
we will be able to attack Immortal Palace and seize the sword.
Seize the sword?
No.
Even with the power of Aquatic Demons,
I'm afraid we can hardly be Luo Ge's opponent.
It would be fine if Yin-yang Cave trapped him,
but we lost our opportunity
because of you.
Fu
did all this?
What?
Both my brother and your brother entered Yin-yang Cave?
At least you can know their news
as soon as possible
if you stay here.
-He was lying to me. -Let me know if you have any news.
How about going to bed and resting for a while?
Or do you want me to make perfume with you?
How could you talk sweetly to me
while plotting
to kill my family?
Although I failed,
I told you
that I wanted to be with Luo Ge.
I never thought of taking Luo Ge's life.
I know.
But think about it.
If Luo Ge
is still an Immortal
or Supreme God,
will you have a chance to be with him?
Whether he is a mortal
or an immortal,
I will definitely be with him.
Great.
But remember,
if you want to be with him,
you have to continue to cooperate with me.
Luo Ge has been busy recovering recently,
and this is our opportunity.
Who is it?
Didn't you say there is a boundary here?
What is that?
How did I feel my brother's aura?
Demon King in White?
My brother wouldn't do such a sneaky thing.
Go back first.
I will let you know
if there is a plan for the next step.
Yes.
Luo Ning!
Who is it?
You killed so many of our fellow disciples!
Yes, it was him. Kill him!
Even if his immortal energy is depleted, he is still an Immortal.
I obviously asked you
to send Liu Shao to Luo Ge.
Remember,
what you want is to get Luo Ge.
And I am for my people.
That person is just one of our pawns.
Luo Ning.
You're awake.
Here.
Thank you.
What happened?
Luo Ning,
I'm really sorry.
I didn't expect Fu
to be so ambitious and reckless.
You don't need to apologize
for him.
Now,
even if he apologizes to me,
I won't forgive him.
From now on,
I will treat him like a stranger.
If he really dares to hurt my brother,
I will definitely kill him.
But you and Fu have already...
So what?
He touched my bottom line
and there is no way I can forgive him anymore.
Although he is excessively cruel,
his feeling for you
is real.
Do you really feel that way?
He keeps saying that he loves me,
but he tries to destroy Immortal Palace and hurt my family.
I don't need
this kind of love.
If he really force me to accept it,
then I'll have to kill him.
Either he dies
or I die.
I just want to ask
if you will
stop him.
I'll go back and tell my brother right away
if you won't.
By then,
I'm afraid
it won't be up to you to deal with it.
You don't have to worry about
the things Fu and Bai Feng discussed.
I will not let Fu have another chance
to leave Demon Palace again.
Got you. You are the traitor.
What's going on here?
Don't deny it!
What's going on?
Why is Xie Lingqi here?
Who allowed you to bring him out?
No, Immortal Master.
Immortal asked us to catch the traitor.
Coincidentally,
we saw this person preparing to escape
after destroying the Four Seasons Monument.
He must be the traitor.
I told you
I was stopped by you
while chasing the real traitor.
Tell me in detail.
What exactly
did you just see?
Well...
Four Seasons Monument was damaged,
and we only saw him running
when we arrived.
That must have been his doing.
Xie Lingqi
Xie Lingqi should have served his sentence under Four Seasons Monument
and now he should be severely punished
for escaping without permission.
I will abolish his cultivation
and interrogate him later.
No.
Immortal Master,
there are still doubts about this matter,
and we cannot make a conclusion now.
Let's investigate first.
Why is he still in Bone Melting Pool
if he's innocent?
You can not convince me with that.
Ge,
you are too softhearted.
If we don't deal with him,
what should we do
if the evil thing becomes stronger?
Take Xie Lingqi back to Bone Melting Pool first,
and forbid him to get out.
Do you have anything else to say?
I'll do as you say.
Madam,
I finally know
why Immortal Ze Shui would kill herself.
It turns out that being extremely disappointed with the one you love
is worse than death.
What's wrong?
Are you worried about me?
Don't worry.
I will not be like Ze Shui.
I'm really disappointed,
but I know what the right thing to do.
Luo Ning!
Luo Ning.
When did you come back?
Why didn't you tell me?
What's wrong?
You don't look well.
Are you hurt?
Who hurt you?
Tell me.
I'll cut him into pieces.
Remember
what you just said to me.
Follow me.
Luo Ning,
what do you come to my brother for?
What happened?
Demon King,
you said
you would deal with it.
Fu.
Come here.
Deal with what?
Does it have anything to do with me?
Or Luo Ning?
Fu.
Do you know what you are doing?
Fairy.
I've sealed his soul pill.
so that he cannot use spells.
And I will imprison him in the Demon Palace
and forbid him to go out for a hundred years.
Are you satisfied?
I don't think
a hundred years
is long enough.
Give him some pens and paper,
and let him transcribe books
to cultivate his mind.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
Just let him transcribe Meditation Spell.
Don't do anything evil,
and do more good things.
Give up evil thoughts
and work hard to cultivate yourself.
Don't do anything evil,
and do more good things.
Give up evil thoughts
and work hard to cultivate yourself.
Luo Ning,
are you despising me
because you blame me for doing too much evil?
It turns out that you are aware of what you have done.
Brother.
Even if I did something wrong,
it was because of a slight error in thought.
Are you really going to
imprison me for a hundred years?
Among the Three Realms,
I respect you the most,
and Luo Ning
is the one I love the most.
You could punish me if I did something wrong.
And I won't complain
even if I am punished by you in a harsh way.
I really didn't expect
that in the end
it would be you
who joined hands to imprison me for a hundred years.
Did I hear it wrong?
After a hundred years,
Luo Ge should be able to become Supreme God.
By then,
I don't have to worry about you working with Bai Feng
to release that evil God
and disrupt the Three Realms.
I'll let you out then.
So last night...
Who is it?
How did I feel my brother's aura?
Demon King in White?
My brother wouldn't do such a sneaky thing.
When did you come back?
Why didn't you tell me?
You said
that you would cut the person who hurt me into pieces.
Didn't you ask me
when I came back?
I came back yesterday.
I heard something
before.
I always thought
that you were just scheming,
but you wouldn't kill innocent people,
nor would you hurt my family.
So,
I borrowed some water energy from your brother.
I tried to use my own eyes
and ears
to
figure out
what kind of person
I once loved is.
Unfortunately,
I heard too much that I shouldn't have heard.
And I was almost
killed by you.
What?
Did I hurt you?
Luo Ning!
I don't need your concern.
Didn't you just promise me
to cut the person who hurt me into pieces?
Now,
you are just going to be held captive for a hundred years.
Luo Ning!
Tree Fairy.
Liu Shao said that you can sense emotions.
Are you
feeling sorry for me now?
They all say you have ten thousand years of memory.
Then tell me
if Ze Shui back then
was
the same as me today?
♫I want to get close but I can't see clearly♫
♫Who arranged this rain?♫
Since you're my husband,
♫I want to avoid but I meet you again♫
you are mine
from now on.
Don’t you ever let me down.
♫I can't help but stay with you♫
I won't.
If I break your heart,
the Brahma tree will wither
♫The stars call the morning sky♫
and I will be alone forever.
♫May you feel relieved♫
♫I long for a hug♫
♫Can I not just listen?♫
♫I want to find our way through destiny♫
♫I want to throw away the memory in exchange for you to come back♫
♫Raise the glass to reincarnate the world♫
♫I'll wait for your response with no regrets♫
♫I'll find the promised home for you♫
♫My heart aches and I will say yes again♫
It turns out
♫When will we separate?♫
Demon King and Immortal Ze Shui
really loved each other so deeply.
♫Please don't tell us our ending in advance♫
Tree Fairy.
Do you remember
anything about the curse?
♫I want to get close but I can't see clearly♫
Ze Shui!
Why did you do this to me?
♫Who arranged this rain?♫
Why did you do this?
How dare you hurt Ze Shui?
♫I want to avoid but I meet you again♫
You and your people
♫I can't help but stay with you♫
will pay for this!
I swear
that your people
♫The endless mountains and seas condensed into raindrops♫
will be imprisoned in the deep water forever,
♫I have walked thousands of miles with the feeling of missing you♫
and that they will die
when they leave the water.
♫I want to ask the prophecy where I should go♫
They will forever be despised
♫For whom did the foreshadowing disappear?♫
and will never be able to see the sun!
♫I want to find our way through destiny♫
Except for me,
this spell can only be lifted
♫I want to throw away the memory in exchange for you to come back♫
when one of Ze Shui's descendants become Demon Queen.
♫Raise the glass to reincarnate the world♫
♫I'll wait for your response with no regrets♫
♫I'll find the promised home for you♫
♫My heart aches and I will say yes again♫
♫When will we separate?♫
♫Please don't tell us our ending in advance♫
What's going on with the Mother of Trees?
She is so excited.
Yes.
Look.
The Mother of Trees...
What's wrong?
It turns out that Immortal Ze Shui
loved him
like I loved Fu.
But she suffered a lot,
and even dragged her people to suffer together.
Luo Ning,
Fu did a lot of wrong things.
I'm really sorry.
I did not teach him well.
I'm his brother.
It's my responsibility.
Have you ever thought
that there might be other ways
to break the curse
besides breaking Four Seasons Monument?
There should
be.
But we tried it before
and it didn't work at all.
Right?
That's because
I only inherited Ze Shui's immortal energy,
but not her resentment.
Even if I tried to think about how to forgive him,
it wouldn’t work.
But
the memory of Brahma tree just show me
that as long as one of Ze Shui's descendants
becomes the Demon Queen,
she will have the right to forgive your people
and lift their ten thousand year curse.